Guide to the Yale Law School Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale Law School records
1820-1961
RU 449
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
38
(93 boxes)
The records consist of correspondence, subject files, finance records, lists, certificates, and miscellaneous papers documenting the activities and operations of the Yale Law School. Topics include admissions, legal societies and associations, publications and journals, bar examinations, commencement, curriculum, faculty, scholarships, and student affairs.
Yale Law School
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 26-A (YRG 26-A), Central records and records of the dean of the Yale Law School
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is partially restricted. See inventory for details
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession
Biographical / Historical
In the first decade of the nineteenth century, Seth P. Staples (Yale 1797) opened a school for law students in New Haven. In 1824 the school became affiliated with Yale College. The college conferred its first law degrees in 1843. The course of study originally extended for two years, and in 1896 it was lengthened to three years. Subsequently a college degree became a prerequisite for the Bachelor of Laws degree. Graduate courses leading to advanced degrees began in 1876. In 1926 honors courses appeared and the school adopted a selective admission process. In 1971, the Yale Corporation authorized the Juris Doctor degree; all candidates for the first professional law degree were awarded the J.D. degree rather than the L.L.B. in 1971. The first Master of Studies in Law degrees were awarded in 1974. The School is housed in its own Gothic-style quadrangle, the Sterling Law Buildings. Completed in 1931, the quadrangle was the g
Scope and Contents
The records consist of correspondence, subject files, finance records, lists, certificates, and miscellaneous papers documenting the activities and operations of the Yale Law School. Topics include admissions, legal societies and associations, publications and journals, bar examinations, commencement, curriculum, faculty, scholarships, and student affairs
Law schools; Law students; Law teachers; Law -- Study and teaching; Universities and colleges -- Administration; Yale Law School; Yale University -- Administration; Yale University -- Admission; Yale University -- Curricula; Yale University -- Faculty; Yale University -- Students
- Law School administrative records, pre 1873; Accession 1939-A-001
  Conditions Governing Access
  The materials are open for research.
  Scope and Contents
  Records removed from the Samuel J. Hitchcock Papers in 1983
  - Correspondence, 1822-1855 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Financial Records, 1843-1852 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous papers re: the Library, 1841-1848, undated. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Lists of students, 1820-1826, 1845-1852? (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Certificates of students' qualifications, 1841-1846 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Circulars, 1843, 1845, undated. (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Office of the Dean records, 1901-1961; Accession 1981-A-014
  Includes correspondence and subject files of the Dean of the Law School
  - General Correspondence, 1946-1954; Series I
    - A, 1946-1955 (Box 1, Folder 1-9)
    - An, 1947-1952, 1953-1955 (Box 1, Folder 10-17)
    - An, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - B, 1946-1954 (Box 2, Folder 19-25)
    - Be, 1946-1954 (Box 2, Folder 26-32)
    - Bi, 1952-1954 (Box 2, Folder 33-34)
    - Bi, 1946-1952 (Box 3, Folder 35-39)
    - Bo, 1946-1954 (Box 3, Folder 40-47)
    - Br, 1948-1954 (Box 3, Folder 48-53)
    - Br, 1946-1948 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Bu, 1946-1954 (Box 4, Folder 55-61)
    - C, 1946-1954 (Box 4, Folder 62-68)
    - Ch, 1946-1954 (Box 5, Folder 69-75)
    - Co, 1949-1954 (Box 5, Folder 76-82)
    - Co, 1946-1949 (Box 6, Folder 81-82)
    - Cor, 1946-1954 (Box 6, Folder 83-89)
    - D, 1949-1954 (Box 6, Folder 90-94)
    - D, 1946-1949 (Box 7, Folder 95-96)
    - Do, 1946-1954 (Box 7, Folder 97-103)
    - E, 1947-1950 (Box 7, Folder 104-106)
    - E, 1946, 1951-1954 (Box 8, Folder 107-111)
    - F, 1946-1954 (Box 8, Folder 112-118)
    - Fo, 1953-1954 (Box 8, Folder 119)
    - Fo, 1946-1953 (Box 9, Folder 120-126)
    - G, 1949-1954 (Box 9, Folder 127-131)
    - G, 1946-1949 (Box 10, Folder 132-133)
    - Go, 1946-1954 (Box 10, Folder 134-141)
    - H, 1952-1954 (Box 10, Folder 142-144)
    - H, 1946-1951 (Box 11, Folder 145-149)
    - Har, 1946-1954 (Box 11, Folder 150-157)
    - He, 1946-1954 (Box 11, Folder 158-164)
    - Ho, 1953-1954 (Box 11, Folder 165)
    - Ho, 1946-1953 (Box 12, Folder 166-171)
    - Hu, 1946-1954 (Box 12, Folder 172-178)
    - I, 1948-1954 (Box 12, Folder 179-184)
    - I, 1946-1948 (Box 13, Folder 185)
    - J, 1946-1954 (Box 13, Folder 186-192)
    - K, 1946-1954 (Box 13, Folder 193-199)
    - Ki, 1946-1954 (Box 14, Folder 200-206)
    - L, 1946-1954 (Box 14, Folder 207-213)
    - Le, 1951-1954 (Box 14, Folder 214-216)
    - Le, 1946-1951 (Box 15, Folder 217-220)
    - Lo, 1946-1954 (Box 15, Folder 221-227)
    - M, 1951-1954 (Box 15, Folder 228-230)
    - M, 1946-1951 (Box 16, Folder 231-234)
    - McA, 1946-1954 (Box 16, Folder 235-241)
    - Me, 1949-1954 (Box 16, Folder 242-246)
    - Me, 1946-1949 (Box 17, Folder 247-248)
    - Mi, 1946-1954 (Box 17, Folder 249-255)
    - Mo, 1946-1954 (Box 17, Folder 256-262)
    - Mu, 1946-1954 (Box 17, Folder 263-270)
    - N, 1953-1954 (Box 17, Folder 271)
    - N, 1946-1953 (Box 18, Folder 272-277)
    - O, 1946-1954 (Box 18, Folder 278-284)
    - P, 1951-1954 (Box 18, Folder 285-287)
    - P, 1946-1951 (Box 19, Folder 288-291)
    - Pi, 1946-1954 (Box 19, Folder 292-298)
    - Q, 1946-1954 (Box 19, Folder 299-305)
    - R, 1953-1954 (Box 19, Folder 306)
    - R, 1946-1953 (Box 20, Folder 307-312)
    - Ri, 1946-1954 (Box 20, Folder 313-319)
    - Ro, 1949-1954 (Box 20, Folder 320-324)
    - Ro, 1946-1949 (Box 21, Folder 325-327)
    - S, 1946-1954 (Box 21, Folder 328-334)
    - Schn, 1948-1954 (Box 21, Folder 335-340)
    - Schn, 1946-1948 (Box 22, Folder 341)
    - Sh, 1946-1954 (Box 22, Folder 342-349)
    - Sm, 1946-1954 (Box 22, Folder 350-356)
    - Sn, 1953-1954 (Box 22, Folder 357)
    - Sn, 1946-1953 (Box 23, Folder 358-363)
    - St, 1946-1954 (Box 23, Folder 364-370)
    - T, 1953-1954 (Box 23, Folder 371)
    - T, 1952-1953 (Box 23, Folder 371a)
    - T, 1951-1952 (Box 23, Folder 372)
    - T, 1946-1951 (Box 24, Folder 373-376)
    - Ti, 1946-1954 (Box 24, Folder 377-383)
    - U, 1949-1954 (Box 24, Folder 384-388)
    - U, 1947-1949 (Box 25, Folder 389-390)
    - V, 1946-1954 (Box 25, Folder 391-397)
    - W, 1946-1954 (Box 25, Folder 398-404)
    - We, 1951-1954 (Box 25, Folder 405-407)
    - We, 1946-1951 (Box 26, Folder 408-411)
    - Wi, 1946-1954 (Box 26, Folder 412-418)
    - Wo, 1946-1954 (Box 26, Folder 419-425)
    - X-Y-Z, 1952-1954 (Box 26, Folder 426-427)
    - X-Y-Z, 1951-1952 (Box 27, Folder 428-429)
    - X-Y-Z, 1949-1950 (Box 27, Folder 430)
    - X-Y-Z, 1946-1949 (Box 27, Folder 431-432)
  - General Correspondence, 1954-1961; Series II
    - A, 1955-1961 (Box 28, Folder 1-6)
    - An, 1958-1961 (Box 28, Folder 7-9)
    - An, 1955-1958 (Box 29, Folder 10-12)
    - B, 1954-1961 (Box 29, Folder 13-20)
    - Be, 1958-1961 (Box 29, Folder 21-23)
    - Be, 1954-1958 (Box 30, Folder 24-27)
    - Bi, 1954-1961 (Box 30, Folder 28-34)
    - Bo, 1956-1961 (Box 30, Folder 35-39)
    - Bo, 1954-1956 (Box 31, Folder 40-41)
    - Br, 1954-1961 (Box 31, Folder 42-48)
    - Bu, 1954-1961 (Box 31, Folder 49-55)
    - C, 1954-1961 (Box 32, Folder 56-62)
    - Ch, 1954-1961 (Box 32, Folder 63-69)
    - Co, 1954-1961 (Box 33, Folder 70-76)
    - Cor, 1955-1961 (Box 33, Folder 77-82)
    - Cor, 1954-1955 (Box 34, Folder 83)
    - D, 1954-1961 (Box 34, Folder 84-90)
    - Do, 1958-1961 (Box 34, Folder 91-93)
    - Do, 1954-1958 (Box 35, Folder 94-97)
    - E, 1954-1961 (Box 35, Folder 98-104)
    - F, 1960-1961 (Box 35, Folder 105)
    - F, 1954-1960 (Box 36, Folder 106-111)
    - Fo, 1956-1961 (Box 36, Folder 112-116)
    - Fo, 1954-1956 (Box 37, Folder 117-118)
    - G, 1954-1961 (Box 37, Folder 119-125)
    - G, 1960-1961 (Box 37, Folder 126)
    - Go, 1954-1960 (Box 38, Folder 127-132)
    - H, 1956-1961 (Box 38, Folder 133-137)
    - H, 1954-1956 (Box 39, Folder 138-139)
    - Har, 1954-1961 (Box 39, Folder 140-146)
    - He, 1956-1961 (Box 39, Folder 147-151)
    - He, 1954-1956 (Box 40, Folder 152-153)
    - Ho, 1954-1961 (Box 40, Folder 154-160)
    - Hu, 1954-1961 (Box 40, Folder 161-167)
    - I, 1954-1961 (Box 40, Folder 168-174)
    - J, 1954-1961 (Box 41, Folder 175-181)
    - K, 1957-1961 (Box 41, Folder 182-185)
    - K, 1954-1958 (Box 42, Folder 186-188)
    - Ki, 1954-1961 (Box 42, Folder 189-195)
    - L, 1954-1961 (Box 42, Folder 196-202)
    - Le, 1959-1961 (Box 42, Folder 203-204)
    - Le, 1957-1959 (Box 43, Folder 205-206)
    - Le, 1954-1957 (Box 44, Folder 207-209)
    - Lo, 1954-1961 (Box 44, Folder 210-216)
    - M, 1958-1961 (Box 44, Folder 217-219)
    - M, 1954-1958 (Box 45, Folder 220-223)
    - McA, 1954-1961 (Box 45, Folder 224-230)
    - Me, 1959-1961 (Box 45, Folder 231-232)
    - Me, 1954-1959 (Box 46, Folder 233-238)
    - Mi, 1954-1961 (Box 46, Folder 239-245)
    - Mo, 1954-1961 (Box 46, Folder 246-253)
    - Mu, 1954-1961 (Box 47, Folder 254-260)
    - N, 1954-1961 (Box 47, Folder 261-267)
    - O, 1954-1961 (Box 48, Folder 268-274)
    - P, 1955-1961 (Box 48, Folder 275-280)
    - P, 1954-1955 (Box 49, Folder 281)
    - Pi, 1959-1961 (Box 49, Folder 282-283)
    - Pi, 1958-1959 (Box 49, Folder 283a)
    - Pi, 1954-1959 (Box 49, Folder 284-287)
    - Q, 1954-1961 (Box 49, Folder 288-293)
    - R, 1959-1961 (Box 49, Folder 294-295)
    - R, 1954-1959 (Box 50, Folder 296-300)
    - Ri, 1954-1961 (Box 50, Folder 301-306)
    - Ri, 1954-1955 (Box 50, Folder 307)
    - Ro, 1954-1961 (Box 51, Folder 308-314)
    - S, 1957-1961 (Box 51, Folder 315-318)
    - S, 1954-1957 (Box 52, Folder 319-321)
    - Schn, 1954-1961 (Box 52, Folder 322-328)
    - Sh, 1959-1961 (Box 52, Folder 329-330)
    - Sh, 1954-1959 (Box 53, Folder 331-335)
    - Sm, 1954-1961 (Box 53, Folder 336-342)
    - Sn, 1958-1961 (Box 53, Folder 343-345)
    - Sn, 1954-1958 (Box 54, Folder 346-349)
    - St, 1955-1961 (Box 54, Folder 350-355)
    - St, 1954-1955 (Box 55, Folder 356)
    - T, 1954-1961 (Box 55, Folder 357-363)
    - Ti, 1956-1961 (Box 55, Folder 364-368)
    - Ti, 1954-1956 (Box 56, Folder 369-370)
    - U, 1954-1961 (Box 56, Folder 371-377)
    - V, 1954-1961 (Box 56, Folder 378-384)
    - W, 1956-1961 (Box 56, Folder 385-390)
    - W, 1954-1956 (Box 57, Folder 391-392)
    - We, 1954-1961 (Box 57, Folder 393-399)
    - Wi, 1956-1961 (Box 57, Folder 400-403)
    - Wi, 1955-1956, 1958-1959 (Box 57, Folder 404-405)
    - Wi, 1954-1955 (Box 58, Folder 406)
    - Wo, 1954-1961 (Box 58, Folder 407-413)
    - X-Y-Z, 1954-1961 (Box 58, Folder 414-420)
  - Subject and Correspondence Files, 1903-1961; Series III
    - Academic Freedom Project: Columbia University, 1951-1953 (Box 59, Folder 1-2)
    - Adams, Paul. W., 1956 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Admissions Committee, 1946-1960 (Box 59, Folder 4-6)
    - Advanced Study Program: summer term, 1948 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Alumni Board: correspondence, reports, and minutes, 1953-1956 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Alumni Day: activities, 1957-1961 (Box 59, Folder 9-10)
    - Alumni Fund, 1946-1947 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Amalgamated Lithographers of America Prize, 1947-1956 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - American Arbitration Association, 1956-1957 (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - American Bar Association: correspondence reports, announcements, 1953-1961 (Box 59, Folder 14-16)
    - American Law Institute, 1946-1947, 1955-1961 (Box 60, Folder 17-18)
    - American Legal Hisotry: research program, 1950 (Box 60, Folder 19)
    - American Legal Studies: Samuel E. Thorne and John P. Frank, 1950 (Box 60, Folder 20)
    - American Association for the Comparative Study of Law, Inc., 1951-1957 (Box 60, Folder 21)
    - Arnold, Thurman W., 1946-1947 (Box 60, Folder 22)
    - Association of American Law Schools, 1954-1959 (Box 60, Folder 23-24)
    - Barristers' Union: participants, reports, 1947-1961 (Box 60, Folder 25-28)
    - Beejamin, Judah P., Fund, 1933-1947 (Box 60, Folder 29)
    - Bittker, Boris, 1945-1946 (Box 61, Folder 30)
    - Blair, Edwin F., 1955-1960 (Box 61, Folder 31-32)
    - Borchard, Edwin M., 1946-1951 (Box 61, Folder 33)
    - Braden, George, 1946-1951 (Box 61, Folder 34)
    - Brandeis, Louis D.; correspondence questioning award of honorary degree, 1927-1930 (Box 61, Folder 34a)
    - Brandeis, Louis D.; correspondence with Brandeis about honorary degree, 1930-1939 (Box 61, Folder 34b)
    - Bromley, Bruce, 1946-1947 (Box 61, Folder 35)
    - Bulletin Board: miscellaneous general notices, 1952-1953 (Box 61, Folder 36)
    - Burnham, Paul S., 1948-1949 (Box 61, Folder 37)
    - Bursar's Office: student accounts, 1955-1960 (Box 61, Folder 38-41)
    - California Bar Examinations; examinees, statistics, 1947-1960 (Box 62, Folder 42-48)
    - Cardozo (Judge): correspondence, 1922 (Box 63, Folder 49)
    - Campus Police: annual reports, 1947-1959 (Box 63, Folder 50-54)
    - Citizens' Charter Committee of New Haven: response, 1949-1950 (Box 63, Folder 55)
    - Civil liberties: pamphlet, 1951 (Box 63, Folder 56)
    - Civil liberties: faculty letters, 1947-1948 (Box 63, Folder 57-58)
    - Clark, Charles E., 1947-1956 (Box 63, Folder 59)
    - Classes of 1947, 1948, 1949, 1950, 1951, 1952, 1953: statistical information (Box 63, Folder 60)
    - Class dinners, reunions, etc., 1947-1953 (Box 64, Folder 61)
    - Colleges--Information re, 1949-1955 (Box 64, Folder 62)
    - Calvin, H. Milton, Tulane Law School, 1933-1934 (Box 64, Folder 63)
    - Commencement--Law School, 1954-1961 (Box 64, Folder 64-67)
    - Commencement--University, 1956-1960 (Box 64, Folder 68)
    - Connecticut Bar, 1954-1960 (Box 64, Folder 70-71)
    - Connecticut Bar, 1946-1953 (Box 65, Folder 72-74)
    - Cooperative Law School Program, 1951 (Box 65, Folder 75)
    - Corbey Court, 1949-1954 (Box 65, Folder 76)
    - (Arthur) Corbin Dinner, 1954 (Box 65, Folder 77)
    - Yale Corporation Votes, 1916-1926 (Box 65, Folder 78-79)
    - Countryman, Vern, 1949-1955 (Box 65, Folder 80)
    - Crawford, A. B., 1946 (Box 65, Folder 81)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1957-1960 (Box 65, Folder 82-83)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1946-1956 (Box 66, Folder 84-87)
    - Davidson, Sidney W., 1948-1959 (Box 66, Folder 88-91)
    - Deanship, 1953 (Box 66, Folder 92)
    - Department of University Health, 1956-1960 (Box 66, Folder 93-94)
    - Department of University Health, 1946-1956 (Box 67, Folder 95-97)
    - Depew, Ganson G. Memorial Fund, 1924-1944 (Box 67, Folder 98)
    - Dession, George H., 1935-1955 (Box 67, Folder 99)
    - Dimock, Edward J., 1946-1947 (Box 67, Folder 100)
    - District of Columbia Bar, 1941-1955 (Box 67, Folder 101)
    - Divisional Program Folder, 1959-1960 (Box 67, Folder 102)
    - Edson, Alex, 1946-1947 (Box 67, Folder 104)
    - Equipment--office supplies, 1948-1960 (Box 67, Folder 105-106)
    - Expenses, 1946-1948 (Box 67, Folder 107)
    - Faculty Meetings, 1947-1954 (Box 68, Folder 108-109)
    - Faculty, New Teaching, 1945-1959 (Box 68, Folder 110-112)
    - Faculty Notices, 1946-1960 (Box 68, Folder 113-120)
    - Fenn, Henry A., 1946-1949 (Box 68, Folder 121)
    - First Year Data, 1936-1947, 1950-1956 (Box 68, Folder 122-123)
    - Florida Bar and Examinations, 1949-1960 (Box 69, Folder 124)
    - Food Law Institute, Inc., 1952 (Box 69, Folder 125)
    - Foreign Nationals, 1952 (Box 69, Folder 128)
    - Forms (samples of applications, etc.), 1936-1955, 1954-1957 (Box 69, Folder 129-131)
    - Fortas, Abe, 1945-1947 (Box 69, Folder 132)
    - LaFayette Foster Professorship, 1903 (Box 69, Folder 134)
    - Four-year Program, 1956-1959, undated (Box 70, Folder 135-136)
    - Frank, Jerome N., 1955-1957 (Box 70, Folder 137)
    - Jerome Frank Association, 1957-1960 (Box 70, Folder 138)
    - Frank, John P., 1949-1954 (Box 70, Folder 139)
    - Fraternities, 1946 (Box 70, Folder 140)
    - Furniss, Edward S., 1946-1956 (Box 70, Folder 141-142)
    - Genocide, 1948-1951 (Box 70, Folder 143)
    - German Graduates, 1951-1952 (Box 70, Folder 144)
    - German Turists, 1949 (Box 70, Folder 145)
    - Gerhard A. Gesell, 1957-1960 (Box 70, Folder 146)
    - Goodhart Fund, 1939-1947 (Box 70, Folder 147)
    - Grading System, 1951-1956 (Box 71, Folder 148)
    - Graduate Board, 1957-1958 (Box 71, Folder 148a-f)
    - Graduate Record Examination, 1945 (Box 71, Folder 149)
    - Graduate School of Yale University, 1929-1960 (Box 71, Folder 150)
    - Graduate Seminar, 1950-1956 (Box 71, Folder 151-153)
    - Graduate students, 1923-1954 (Box 71, Folder 154)
    - Haber, David, 1946-1955 (Box 71, Folder 155)
    - Hallstein, Walter, 1947 (Box 71, Folder 156)
    - Hand, Chauncey H., 1946-1948 (Box 71, Folder 157-158)
    - Harper, Fowler, 1947-1957 (Box 71, Folder 159)
    - Harvard Law School, 1945-1961 (Box 72, Folder 160-165)
    - Hicks, F. C., 1946-1956 (Box 72, Folder 166)
    - Hoober, John A., 1946-1947 (Box 72, Folder 167)
    - Housing, 1946 (Box 72, Folder 168)
    - Housing Committee--Yale University, 1950-1960 (Box 72, Folder 169)
    - Illinois Bar Examinations, 1936-1956 (Box 72, Folder 170)
    - Institute for International Order, 1955-1957 (Box 72, Folder 171)
    - Institute of International Education, 1956-1960 (Box 72, Folder 172)
    - James, Fleming, Jr., 1946 (Box 72, Folder 173)
    - Judge's gavel, 1940-1942 (Box 72, Folder 174)
    - Kessler, Friedrich, 1946 (Box 73, Folder 175)
    - Laski, Harold, 1929-1939, 1951 (Box 73, Folder 176)
    - Law Aptitude Examination, 1945-1950 (Box 73, Folder 177-179)
    - Law Buildings, 1956-1960 (Box 73, Folder 180-182)
    - Law Buildings, 1952-1956 (Box 74, Folder 183-184)
    - Law Journal, 1946-1959 (Box 74, Folder 185-191)
    - Law Library-General, 1946-1959 (Box 75, Folder 192-197)
    - Law Professors, 1946-1947 (Box 75, Folder 198)
    - Law School Admission Test, 1951-1959 (Box 75, Folder 199-200)
    - Law School Admission Test, 1950-1953 (Box 76, Folder 201)
    - Law School Alumni Association, 1955-1956 (Box 76, Folder 202)
    - Law School Alumni Fund., 1952-1955 (Box 76, Folder 203)
    - Law School Association, 1952-1961 (Box 76, Folder 204-207)
    - Law School Building, New, 1945-1950 (Box 77, Folder 208)
    - Law School Dances, Student Association, 1931-1946 (Box 77, Folder 209)
    - Law School Forum, 1946-1953 (Box 77, Folder 210-212)
    - Law School Student Association, 1946-1948, 1953-1959 (Box 77, Folder 213-216)
    - Law School Studies, 1949-1951 (Box 78, Folder 217)
    - Lectures--General, 1936-1946 (Box 78, Folder 218)
    - Legal Aid, 1946-1959 (Box 78, Folder 219-223)
    - Legal Aptitude Test, 1935, 1941 (Box 78, Folder 224)
    - Legal Ethics, 1954 (Box 78, Folder 225)
    - Legal Research, 1951-1956 (Box 79, Folder 226)
    - Lemkin, Raphael, 1951-1956 (Box 79, Folder 227)
    - Library--University, 1927-1956 (Box 79, Folder 228)
    - Lohmann, Carl A., 1927-1953 (Box 79, Folder 230)
    - Lowenstein, Karl, 1934-1948 (Box 79, Folder 231)
    - Lorenzen, Ernest G., 1946-1951 (Box 79, Folder 232)
    - McDougal, Myres S., 1934-1956 (Box 79, Folder 233-234)
    - Mimeographing, 1946-1947 (Box 79, Folder 235)
    - Moore, James W., 1934-1946 (Box 79, Folder 236)
    - Moore, Underhill, 1946-1949 (Box 79, Folder 237)
    - Moot Court, 1957-1959 (Box 79, Folder 238-239)
    - Moot Court, 1952-1956 (Box 80, Folder 240)
    - Mueller, Addison A., 1943-1947 (Box 80, Folder 241)
    - National Committee for Clarifying the Constitution, 1940 (Box 80, Folder 242)
    - National Consumer's League, 1940(?) (Box 80, Folder 243)
    - National Labor Relations Board, 1940(?) (Box 80, Folder 244)
    - New York Bar and Examinations, 1948-1961 (Box 80, Folder 245-252)
    - New York Bar and Examinations, 1945-1948 (Box 81, Folder 253)
    - Newsletter (Law School), 1950-1952, 1951-1954 (Box 81, Folder 254-256)
    - Newspaper Releases, 1946, 1950-1952, 1956-1959 (Box 81, Folder 257-259)
    - Nyman, R. Carter, Personnel Director, 1940-1949 (Box 81, Folder 260)
    - Ohio Bar and Examinations, 1938-1957 (Box 81, Folder 261)
    - Order of the Coif, 1946-1959 (Box 82, Folder 262-265)
    - Oregon Bar, 1951-1953 (Box 82, Folder 266)
    - Paul, Randolph E./Visiting Sterling Lecturer, 1937-1946 (Box 82, Folder 267)
    - Pennsylvania Bar and Examinations, 1933-1960 (Box 82, Folder 268-269)
    - Personnel Study, Department of Psycological Tests, 1938-1941 (Box 82, Folder 270)
    - Phi Beta Kappa Announcements, Yale, 1938-1946 (Box 82, Folder 271)
    - Posters, 1955-1959, 1957-1960 (Box 83, Folder 272-274)
    - Post-War Planning Committee--Connecticut Committee, 1945 (Box 83, Folder 275)
    - Post-War Planning Committee--General (Box 83, Folder 276)
    - President's Conference of Scientists and Engineers, 1958 (Box 83, Folder 277)
    - Prices--regarding mimeographing examinations, 1953 (Box 83, Folder 278)
    - Prizes--Gallagher, 1946-1954 (Box 83, Folder 279)
    - Prizes--general, 1936-1948 (Box 83, Folder 280)
    - Prizes--Jewell, 1936-1946 (Box 83, Folder 281)
    - Prizes--Nathan Burkan Memorial, 1940-1958 (Box 83, Folder 282-283)
    - Rand Corporation, 1948 (Box 84, Folder 284)
    - Research Assistants, 1928-1935, 1946-1952 (Box 84, Folder 285-286)
    - Research Committee, 1931-1932 (Box 84, Folder 287)
    - Walter and Lucie Rose Foundation, Inc., 1945 (Box 84, Folder 288)
    - Rostow, Eugene V., 1956-1958 (Box 84, Folder 289-290)
    - Schedules, 1936-1959 (Box 84, Folder 291-295)
    - Scholarships--Crippled Children's Friendly Aid Association, 1935-1951 (Box 84, Folder 296)
    - Scholarships--John A. Hoober, 1927-1949 (Box 84, Folder 297)
    - Scholarships--Kappa Beta Pi, 1927-1929 (Box 84, Folder 298)
    - Scholarships--Herbert R. Limburg Fund, 1936 (Box 84, Folder 299)
    - Scholarships--John A. Annie Low, 1935-1938 (Box 85, Folder 300)
    - Scholarships--Morris, 1938-1939 (Box 85, Folder 301)
    - Scholarships--Richard Martin Paskus Memorial, 1939-1949 (Box 85, Folder 302)
    - Scholarships--Patrol Office, 1934 (Box 85, Folder 303)
    - Scholarhsips--Pine, 1935-1943 (Box 85, Folder 304)
    - Scholarships--Lucien B. and Katherine E. Price Foundation, 1938 (Box 85, Folder 305)
    - Scholarhsips--Thacher, 1930-1931 (Box 85, Folder 307)
    - Scholarships--Woolsey, 1926-1930 (Box 85, Folder 308)
    - Secretarial Staff, 1948-1961 (Box 85, Folder 309)
    - Secretary's Office, 1946-1960 (Box 85, Folder 310-313)
    - Segal, Harry M., 1920-1922 (Box 85, Folder 314)
    - Service Bureau, 1942-1958 (Box 85, Folder 315-316)
    - Seymour, President Charles, 1947-1950 (Box 85, Folder 317-318)
    - Seymour, Whitney N., 1937-1948 (Box 85, Folder 319)
    - Shulman, Harry, 1929-1955 (Box 85, Folder 320)
    - Harry Shulman Conference, 1957-1958 (Box 86, Folder 321)
    - Shulman Dinner, 1954-1955 (Box 86, Folder 322)
    - Smith, J. Allen, 1958-1960 (Box 86, Folder 324)
    - State Reports, ?-1944 (Box 86, Folder 325)
    - Statistics, 1949-1960 (Box 86, Folder 326-329)
    - Sterling Law Buildings, 1931-1938 (Box 86, Folder 330)
    - Steffen, Roscoe T., 1940-1949 (Box 86, Folder 331)
    - Stenographer's Applications, 1951-1956 (Box 86, Folder 332)
    - Stephan, Frederick F./American Statistical Association, 1936 (Box 86, Folder 333)
    - Storrs Lectures, 1938-1956 (Box 87, Folder 335)
    - Sturges, Wesley A., 1955-1961 (Box 87, Folder 336)
    - Summer Session, 1948, 1950 (Box 87, Folder 337-338)
    - Taft, William Howard, 1919-1941 (Box 87, Folder 339)
    - Taxation Course, 1947-1948 (Box 87, Folder 340)